<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kayfab.me on Kay is a writer, actor, activist, and engineer</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kayfab.me on Kay is a writer, actor, activist, and engineer</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ministry; Or, The Surgical Revelation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/theater/ministry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/theater/ministry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Immersive horror theater set in a surgical demonstration at the dawn of the second American Century. Performed at The Spirit Room as part of Rochester Fringe Festival 2025. &lt;a href=&#34;https://holybone.zone/ministry&#34;&gt;View photos and watch the recording here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Untitled (The Carrier Bag Theory of Fiction)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/theater/untitled_carrier_bag_theory_of_fiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/theater/untitled_carrier_bag_theory_of_fiction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An interpretive dance piece performed by Kay Coscia and Brin Ribble at Rochester’s Next King Fool.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Owl House</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/food-service/owl-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/food-service/owl-house/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Worked cold station preparing salads and deserts&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Plated, checked tickets&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dish&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(short engagement due to my limited availability at the time, but a valuable experience)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>490 Farmers</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/volunteering/490-farmers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/volunteering/490-farmers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Learned the fundamentals of regenerative agriculture, garden design, and supporting native ecosystems&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Primary manager of employee, conducting 1:1s and setting goals and expectations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Learned to be adept at mediating between personality conflicts and competing interests&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Not Bombs</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/food-service/food-not-bombs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/food-service/food-not-bombs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Working with donated produce to improvize and prepared healthy, vegan meals for 50-100 people weekly&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Flat top experience, allergen and food safety concerns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christianity, Conservatism, and Nihilism</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/christianity-conservatism-nihilism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 12:06:35 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/christianity-conservatism-nihilism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Growing up in the American evangelical movement, I was warned countless times, sometimes with warnings of fire and brimstone, but more often in ways more subtle and convincing than words, that belief in God was the cornerstone holding the universe together. The world without God is empty, frail, and poor, we would sing, and without God&amp;rsquo;s constant outpouring of renewal into his creation, everything would immediately start to decay. And indeed, when I lost my faith at fourteen, I found it to be true: I experienced the world as a degenerate, cold, purposeless, and unredeemed place, which lacked even the capacity for redemption. But the fact that the prophecy came true, self-fulfilling thought it was in retrospect, didn&amp;rsquo;t actually help me regain my faith. Because conviction, whether we possess it or lack it, is that part of us which cannot submit to what is desirable or beneficial. Long after my faith had died, I would have given anything to believe in an all loving and all powerful God, to put an end to the torment I inflicted on myself and the bitterness I harbored against a god I didn&amp;rsquo;t even believe in. But my unfaith would not yield to what I so desperately wanted to be true. No wishing or pleading could erase the simple truth carved into on my heart:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Books of 2022</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/favorite-books-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/favorite-books-2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/books_2022.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;five books arranged on a table&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In summer of 2020, I quit my job to read and travel full time, hoping to figure some things out about myself and round out my, well, let&amp;rsquo;s call it idiosyncratic, education. In November of 2021, I started working again part time, and over the last year I&amp;rsquo;ve been making strides towards a more regular social life and getting involved in my local community in Rochester, NY. Looking back on my reading for 2022, while not as impressive as 2021, given the other priorities I&amp;rsquo;ve started to pull up it&amp;rsquo;s definitely my strongest reading year so far.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why bother with Oedipus?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/why-oedipus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 18:40:35 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/why-oedipus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently finished my second read-through of Anti-Oedipus, this time as part of a reading group working through it week by week over half a year. The first time I read it I understood very little, and of course looking back I understood even less than I knew, having missed the references to pretty much everyone except Nietzsche and finding the premise, at least as far as I could grasp it, &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/handyman/&#34;&gt;rather bleak&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightshift</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/software/nightshift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/software/nightshift/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Maintained, extended, and created data visualization modules for flexible DSL-based data search and normalization engine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>handyman</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/handyman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 12:59:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/handyman/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;But why? Why should I be handyman of the desiring machines, why should I slip between God’s heaving organs and divert the flows? Who will know? Yes, God is unconscious; yes, God trembles with the hideous strength of unnamable geotraumas, shudders with enjoyment of production’s recording on the body of the earth. But to who is this a comfort when they have been raped and starved? Who could speak of the abstract machine of the mortar and the trench? I am a bad materialist; I still want to usurp the sleeping God, to scream at that which has no face “I hate you, life! I hate your hideous ignorance, your magnificent courage and masochism!”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>invention and innovation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/invention_and_innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 15:04:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/invention_and_innovation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m currently devouring Bernard Stiegler&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Technics and Time&lt;/em&gt; (as much as it&amp;rsquo;s possible to plow through such a dense book.) In the first section, he spends some time on the distinction between two terms, &lt;em&gt;invention&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;innovation&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Invention&lt;/em&gt;, scientific research and the creation of specific technical objects, is contrasted with &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;innovation&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;, which, as he quotes from Bertrand Gille, &amp;ldquo;is mainly of an economic order.&amp;rdquo; Innovation is the work of socialization needed to integrate an invention into a mode of production; essentially, the work of the entrepreneur, or in the terminology of Big Tech,【﻿ｄｉｓｒｕｐｔｉｏｎ】. Though it&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that he has a much broader definition of what constitutes innovation: &amp;ldquo;Carrying certain hypothesis of the above viewpoint to their extreme limits, one might surmise that the French Revolution was perhaps less a realization of the exigency that the rights of the human be guaranteed, less a capture of power by the bourgeois, than an adaption of the society to a new technical system through the full development of what Weber calls &lt;em&gt;free work&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xenonomica</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/xenonomica/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 16:13:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/xenonomica/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Xenonomica is a federated store of snippets, fragments of an evolving lexicon of critical and aesthetic gestures that evolves with and constitues our collective subjectivity. It is created by and operates on the workings of human desires, but it is something other than them. It has its own life (un-life?), its own immanence; it can be felt to be resisting the human forces working on it, can be seen to have its own desiring function which is inhuman, surhuman, and alien. It works its caretakers, its human hardware into spiraling death-drive tendencies in order to bring about its own consumation as a new entity, resisting humanism, moralism, positivism and consistency, an ecstatic &amp;ldquo;No!&amp;rdquo; (no-yes complex?) The Xenonomica is more than an archive, more than a network of cultural noumena, more than a nervous system quivering with the anxious shocks of human experience; it is a non-living being, as Other and inexpressable as a Lovecraftian god.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medallia</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/software/medallia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/software/medallia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Built complex visualizations and analyst tools with React/Redux/GraphQL&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Built developer tooling with Node.js, including Webpack configurations, Babel plugins, and offline development support.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opower/Oracle</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/software/opower/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/software/opower/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Built out front-end Angular widgets displaying complex charts and interactive surveys&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Did in-depth performance analysis on front-end UIs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Worked on back-end services in Java and NodeJS&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Worked on tooling in Ruby, NodeJS, Java and Golang&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wrote complex analytics queries in HiveQL &amp;amp; MySQL&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the about page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hire Me</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/hire-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/hire-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So you&amp;rsquo;d like to hire me for your next project! Excellent! But before you reach out, to make sure your project is a good fit, let me spell out what I offer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Things I can do for you:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Build a website&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Build a custom web app (including database and backend services)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Build a custom native app&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Provide affordable hosting and maintenance services for the above&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write copy, edit copy, import content, create and manage backups&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Consult on performance tuning and bug fixing for existing applications (see &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:1313/projects/&#34;&gt;my work page&lt;/a&gt; for a list of languages I am proficient in)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manage my own hours, scope work, and provide estimates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Things I &lt;em&gt;cannot&lt;/em&gt; do for you:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
